Thank you for watching!
Thanks again for all your hard work!
Hello! Stay, this time with Sakura Ishiyama of JuiceJuice and
and Sumide Tashiro from Ocha-no-Uma!
This time, we're going to show you the two of them, so please bear with us until the end.
Thank you very much for your cooperation!
JuiceJuice's fall tour concert will be held on December 6th.
The final concert of JuiceJuice's fall tour will be held at Nippon Budokan on December 6.
Yes, this fall tour will be a combination of JuiceJuice's history and JuiceJuice's music, and it will be a mixture of Juice and JuiceJuice's music.
This fall tour is titled "Juice Story", which is a mixture of JuiceJuice's history and Juice's story.
It's really filled with the history of JuiceJuice for the past 10 years.
Even if you are a newcomer, you can learn a lot of songs like this.
For those who have been supporting JuiceJuice for a long time, there are a lot of nostalgic songs.
I think this tour will be a lot of fun.
Ocha no Ma's first album
Channel 1 will be released on January 10 next year. This album contains 23 songs, including 5 new songs, on 2 discs.
I think it's really full of the songs we've been singing so far, so please look forward to listening to it.
Hello Project 2024winter 3 of us will start on January 2nd next year.
I'll be performing as team b with Juice Juice, to which I belong, and Tea Mat, to which Sumire Taishiro belongs, and Angeleume.
I'm really looking forward to seeing the songs that can only be seen by the three groups, and I'm not sure what kind of songs we'll have if we have all the songs.
Please take a look at the video below.
Haloste is about to start.
No, no, no, the show is about to start.
It's about to start.
I'm already nervous.
I'm like, "I'm having fun," but it's definitely fun.
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best to see it.
It's Haloste.
Haloste.
Yes, I can do it.
Yes, I can.
Let's have fun.
It's 10:00.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
It's okay.
Everyone,
Finally,
HIPHOP video is over.
No graduation.
I'm live.
That's right. Let's show everything we have now.
And after all, we have to enjoy ourselves the most and convey that to you.
We have to take care of that.
We'll deliver what we need to deliver.
I'm nervous.
I think everyone is nervous, including me,
We are cool!
We have a great cover!
We are the best, so we are the best!
Everyone be confident,
Let's get our acceptance on stage.
Gacon!
Kamiko!
Leila!
Kero!
Tame!
Waka-nyan!
Yup!
Keep Your Earth!
Let's do our best!
Sparkling like a flower, aren't they?
Sparkling.
Let's keep up the good work.
Thank you for your hard work.
Really? I can't believe you landed on the database.
I've been warming up to it.
I've been warming up, worrying over it, getting excited, and today's cote...
It's nonsense to say that it's moderate.
It's for your own good... the sensitivity of love.
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Red live, this kiss is proof that I'm ready
Proof that I'm ready
I do I do
Red Live
If you miss me, I'll show you the rainbow's head
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Even if you look like you've done it
See? So tell me...
What's it like in your heart?
I have pain
Me
Me.
me
me me me
Innocent love, two hands on top of each other
But I'm sure it won't mean anything and I'll forget it
Once I get to know your special
I'll go to any pad I'll go to any pad I'll go to any pad I'll go to any pad
I want to cross the bed line I want to get hurt I want to hurt you
I do I do I do I'm ready
I'm ready
Let's go right
Fireworks to say goodbye
I do I do I confide in you
Let's go right
Let's go right together
Sakura Ishiyama of Juice Juice
and Sumire Tashiro of Ocha no Ma present Haloste.
I'd like to talk a little bit about each other from here.
I'm going to ask you some questions.
So let's answer them quickly and without thinking too much.
Okay, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Only about one month left in 2023.
What do you think you have left to do?
To go to a summer festival in the summer.
What trends are you interested in this winter?
Hats
First album will be released on January 10 next year
Channel 1 will be released on January 10!
It's a little early, but what can we expect to hear on the album?
I think it is full of the charm of tea horses!
What is the secret of your cuteness?
Sleeping.
Hello Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
What songs have you found new appealing since the 25th anniversary?
The horse of tea, the horse of tea, Mahoroba Ikoi no Ma (The horse of tea, the horse of tea, Mahoroba Ikoi no Ma)
Showa and 2025 are all over the place!
My favorite song too!
I heard that you couldn't go to the first summer festival.
Do you go to many summer festivals?
I haven't been to a summer festival since I was little.
I haven't been to one since I was little, but this year I really wanted to go.
I talked with the members about going together, but we couldn't find a good day to go, so I'm sorry I couldn't go.
By the way, what do you eat at summer festivals? I love strawberry candy at summer festivals.
I'll definitely eat strawberry candy. Wow, that looks delicious.
I asked you the secret to your cuteness.
Sleep is important, isn't it? Sleep is important.
If you don't sleep you get dark circles.
So, please sleep. How long do you sleep? I usually go to bed around...
I usually go to bed around midnight.
I usually go to bed around midnight and wake up around 8:00 or 9:00 a.m. It's very healthy, isn't it?
I'm very healthy, aren't I?
I don't know... smells. Smells?
Smells? Relaxing smells. The kind you spray on your pillow.
I like that, actually, so I have a nice-smelling aroma.
I really like it, I really like it, so I can cry and sleep with peace of mind, so I recommend it.
Questions for Mr. Ishiyama after the VTR
Hello! I really like it.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great!
That one lie is the end of everything.
Morning Musume。23 す すごいフィーバー
Now on sale
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
Taiyo Hato Moto
Morning Musume。23 Wake up call
Wake up call Now on sale
If I may say so, what a stupid mama human being
Morning Musume。23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine Now on sale
Koukou de Red Line Hurt, I want to hurt, I want to hurt
I do I do Ai no Saber
Angstrom Red Line December 13
Now on sale
Life is opening up with my mouth, quite full, very sad.
I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do I do
Life is beautiful
Angulum Life is beautiful Dec 13 Now on sale
Angulum Concert Tour 2023 Autumn 11 Angulum's Best 11 is over!
How was it? Yup.
Yes, it was a lot of fun.
It ended without a hitch.
I feel like I've done it all.
I was really happy to perform "Red Line" and "Life isbeautiful" on stage.
I'd like to perform with Hana-chan next time.
It was so much fun!
Yup, you did a great job with Hana-chan, didn't you?
Yes, I did!
Let's see Akero-chan!
How was it?
Well, it felt like the final show of the fall tour.
I think...
The set was also ready for the tour.
I bought a suit and everything.
But it was a special show, wasn't it?
Yes, it was.
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
How was Shion's?
Yes.
Well, it's been a year.
It's been a year since we've been in the same room as Angstrom.
Thank you very much.
I was really happy to be in this video.
I'm so happy that I could make it with everyone!
Once again, I felt so happy that we could do Budokan without graduation.
You've already done it today, haven't you?
Yes, I did!
Thank you very much for a great live performance!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now.
That's all for now!
Haloste!
Next, I would like to ask Ms. Ishiyama some questions.
I'll do my best.
Today is a good clothes day in Japanese.
Which of today's outfits is good for you?
Wintery knitwear
December 6 is the third Nippon Budokan concert this year.
What do you want to show on the next stage based on the past two performances?
I would like to share my performance and charm with each and every person who comes to the concert.
If you were to make a movie about Sakura Ishiyama in 2023, what would the title be?
Sakura Ishiyama 2023
What is the food you are addicted to now?
Iekei Ramen
Which song from Hello Project's past songs would you like to perform because you are the person you are now?
Angulum's "Endless Moments
Thank you very much.
I thought today's outfit was very cute and wintery.
Is that true? I just wore what I had around here.
It's really cute.
So you're into ramen now?
Yes, I like white rice.
I like ramen and white rice, and they go really well together.
I'm also a big fan of ramen.
That's right.
The thinness of the noodle depends on the restaurant.
I'm addicted to looking around the ramen shops to see if the noodles are thin or not, and if the ajitama is broken or not.
I'm addicted to exploring.
That's great!
If you make a movie about Sakura Ishiyama in 2023...
Ishiyama Sakura 2023.
Yes, sir.
I want to hear it.
I wonder...
I want to make a movie about my events that happened only in 2023.
I want to make a lot of movies.
I would love to make a movie in 2023
to a sequel in 2024.
I'd love to see
Haloste will continue after this.
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is Natsuyaki Kimiyabi
I'm Momo Kitahara, the tea lady.
What would you like to make this time?
Yes, I would like to make mushroom risotto.
I've really been longing for this dish at Hello Kitchen.
I've been secretly looking forward to it for a long time.
I'm very happy, I'll do my best.
When you get to the middle, it's not safe, so take it down again.
A little to the side.
Clear, clear, clear!
I did it!
So, doctor, what would you like to start with?
Risotto!
We're going to fry the rice.
Don't wash the rice, ever.
Why?
Because if you wash it, it gets too sticky.
If you wash the rice, it will become too sticky and sludgy.
Of course, risotto is very sticky.
But it becomes more like porridge.
Oh, you're right.
You want each grain of rice to stand up a little bit.
Yes.
Like this.
I didn't wash the pan I cooked the mushrooms in last time.
So, medium heat, low Chinese heat.
Sprinkle some salt on the onions.
And how much salt?
About 1 gram of salt.
Yes, please put it in.
Now it becomes transparent.
Aromatic, right? Onions.
Yes, it does.
And now, prepare this.
So you're already doing that?
Yes, fry the rice.
Yes, fry.
Yes, and I don't mean fry the rice.
Yes.
You coat the rice with the aroma of butter and onions.
Momochan and I sang a song together once on YouTube.
The Curse of Love.
Yes, we sang together in a wonderful project.
You know, you've become a much older sister than you were then.
Yay!
Was it a long time ago? Well then...
What's that? Did you film it? Always?
When was it?
Well, last year?
About a year ago.
It takes a year to change. I knew girls change really quickly.
They grow up in a year. They really do.
Just pour me a couple of drinks.
I'm motivated!
Oh!
That's great, great, great!
It's only the first time, you know, the first time.
So this is going to gradually absorb the water?
That's right.
This is the first time, but it's only the first time.
I put this in again, in the middle.
And please stir it gently.
Momochan is very expressive, sir.
More?
More than anyone.
I've been talking about it to my manager.
I've been telling her how great you are.
Which part? When she sings?
When she sings, and also when other people are singing, she can make facial expressions.
So you watch her that closely!
You're watching me!
I thought you were watching me.
I do!
You're scary.
Don't tell me I'm scaring you.
I'm watching you.
I'm glad.
Mix it up!
Let me in!
Let it in! Let it in!
Yeah, I know, I'm like that.
Two cups?
One, two.
I see a lot of younger students, and I think they're great members.
Momochan, I'm so happy for you right now.
Recently, I'd like to recommend and recommend
My guess!
Oh no!
I'm a little nervous when you say "guess".
I'm a little nervous, aren't I?
But it's definitely risotto-like.
It's really good.
Not like this, but like risotto.
Can you see how it's getting a little bit puffy?
It's swelling up.
I see it.
One more, maybe.
But, you know, with the tea, what do you want to do? From now on.
We are currently on a 47 prefectures tour.
That's great.
We've been talking about doing it for a long time.
That's one of my dreams come true.
I would also like to go overseas.
Ocha-noma" is taken from "Ocha-noma? It's taken from "Ocha-no-Ma," which means "Tea Room.
Ochanoma means a place where you can relax.
It's something Japanese.
It's a kind of culture.
I sing songs while learning about Japanese culture.
I want to spread that kind of thing to people overseas.
The members of the band have been talking about how we would like to expand our business overseas.
That's a good dream and a good goal.
It's different with today's kids.
They have their eyes on the world.
That's true.
You also want to go to Europe.
Cooking.
I didn't get the chance to train there.
But there are things you learn by going there.
On the other hand, you can see the good qualities of Japan by going abroad.
That's true.
Yes, that's true.
Just a little bit.
About two grains.
Two or three grains.
I'm just checking to see if there's a core.
If it's hard, that's it.
Taste
Mmm-hmm.
Is it good?
It's really good.
It's good?
The rice isn't hard anymore.
Yes, it is.
Let's do it here.
Oh!
The point of peach vinegar.
Never burn the finish!
Cute!
I'm definitely going to screenshot this.
I'm sending it to my sister.
Bon appétit!
Okay, I'm going to drain off as much water as possible at the end.
It's really, really, really good.
If you leave it unattended, it will burn.
Careful, careful.
But I want to remove all the moisture.
You just said that.
Right.
Okay, now, put the mushrooms back in.
Don't you think we lost some of the mushrooms?
Certainly.
That's for sure.
There were so many in the beginning.
Yes, you're right.
You thought it was too much.
Dr. Bishop, you must have thought it was the wrong amount.
No, no, no, no, no.
The cheese is added at the end, and once it's warmed up, it's ready to eat.
More or less.
But not too much.
It was easy, wasn't it?
Better than I imagined.
It's ready, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
It's ready, yes.
Now let's put it on the plate.
Wow, that's a lot of cheese. That's hard to do.
I can drink it. It's okay, it's okay. In the middle.
Let's make a mountain out of it. Make a mountain out of it.
In a restaurant, it's cool to serve it like this already.
Sure, this time.
There's more.
Cured ham. Looks good.
Cured ham, you know, as much air as you can wrap inside.
Wash your hands a little bit, and then at the end, like one, two, three, four, five, diagonally.
On the edge. Yes, OK.
Wow, very stylish!
Yes, now it's done?
It's done!
Mushroom risotto is ready!
How do you like it, Momo?
Well, it looks really stylish, and the diagonal line of black pepper is really cool,
You worked so hard to make it so skinny.
I'm glad. I'm glad I could make such a nice dish.
Now, please try the risotto that Momo-chan worked so hard on.
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious.
Bon appétit.
Here it is.
Yum!
Wonderful!
The mushroom flavor is stronger than I expected.
After all, you didn't throw away the mushroom broth, or rather, the flavor of the mushrooms.
You didn't throw away the flavor of the mushrooms, did you?
You didn't throw away the flavor of the mushrooms, and it soaks into the rice.
That's why you can taste the mushrooms.
It's really delicious.
And the texture of the rice...
How was it?
Al dente.
That's a fancy way of putting it.
I thought it was al dente.
That's cool.
It's really good.
Good, good, good.
How was it, doctor? Kinomo-chan.
There's no chance...
There's really no chance.
I dare say so.
That's true.
At first.
I said I don't usually cook much.
I was a little nervous with the knife.
You'll get used to it.
But it was fun, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
That's great.
I'm glad you said you wanted to be in Hello Kitchen.
I'm so glad that I was able to perform with you this time.
Thank you very much.
I hope you'll make use of what you learned this time.
I hope you'll make the most of this experience and try cooking at home too.
I will!
That's all for now, Hello Kitchen!
Bye bye!
Looks delicious!
So, do you have any recent dishes you've made?
Well, I recently made onigiri.
Onigiri have a variety of ingredients.
Among them, I like cod roe the best.
I bought cod roe, cooked some rice, and wrapped it in nori seaweed.
I took it to work and ate it, and it was so delicious.
I kept eating it.
Is that okay?
I've been slacking lately.
Oh, I skipped it.
So I'd like to get back into it.
Well, I recently made takikomi gohan.
I made takikomi gohan with mushrooms and chicken, and I thought it turned out really delicious.
I thought it tasted really good, but the taste was very weak.
So today is November 29th, which is a good meat day...
Yes, I'm Ishiyama!
I, Ishiyama, am a great lover of yakiniku (grilled meat)
I love yakiniku!
I eat belly, tongue, and meat.
I love belly and meat, and I also love seseri.
What does seseri taste like?
It's kind of like chicken meat, but it's delicious!
I'm sure you'll love it!
It's really delicious and I love it!
I want to try seseri.
Please eat it!
Hello! Next is the presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart!
What is the best lyric or phrase for the season when the year is coming to an end?
I chose the lyrics "I'm always thinking of you and want to tell you thank you" from JuiceJuice's song Familia, because I feel like the year is over and I want to thank everyone and move on to the next year.
How about you? I'm Yataru-chan by S/mileage and the lyrics are about how I want to be Yataru-chan at all times.
I think it's a song that gives me a lot of courage, and I listen to it all year round, and spend my time thinking, "I want to be Yaru-chan, too.
I think it's so cute that I'm going to spend the next year like Yataru-chan too.
I love it so much! Please watch the VTR now.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello Project songs that have touched our hearts and talk about their charms.
You can also listen to the lyrics of the songs on the "Hello! I hope you will be able to understand the charm of the song.
Yes! I've got guts, don't I?
This week, I, Shuotoni, will be presenting.
Here it is.
Ta-da!
Please call me.
You should like all human beings.
Life is one time
Great song!
Morning Musume。 This is Mikan from Morning Musume。
This song is good.
I understand.
It's not about what's good about it.
It's all of them,
I think it's the one that sticks with me the most,
All of it.
Life is a one-time event.
That's really true.
Because, you know, there may be a previous life, or a next life, or whatever,
I'm living the life I remember now, and that means I only live it once,
That's something already,
Even when I am talking like this, it is in the past, and the phrase I just said is also in the past,
When I think about it, I get a deep feeling that life is long but short.
Also, there is a four-character phrase that I like to read in a magazine,
Proverb?
It has a proverb, "Laughing in conflict brings good fortune. I like it very much,
It's like, if you laugh only once in your life, you will be blessed,
I said it in a very light-hearted way,
It's really hard to put into words.
It's really hard to put into words, but in my head, I think it's like this,
But when I talk with YUTPYOU on a daily basis, I realize that I only live once,
I can really feel that he is enjoying his time.
Is that so?
I feel like he is the person behind the lyrics.
Yes, yes, yes.
I like him, so I'm influenced by him.
Yeah, yeah. You're influenced by him.
I like all these people a lot.
I understand.
I get it.
I got it.
Yeah, what?
It's Anju, isn't it?
It's the same thing, but having someone you don't like,
It's not fun, is it?
Oh, I understand.
It's not fun, and nothing good has come out of it for me,
So, even if we don't agree with each other, we can't disagree on the parts we don't agree on,
So, if we don't fit together, the opposite is true,
So, if we don't fit together, the opposite can be turned around and become a good thing.
Everyone has their own good points,
I don't want to go to the point of disliking them,
That's right.
I really like everyone.
I understand.
Yes. How about Hanana?
No, it's really the same.
That's right.
I want to tell them that they have one life, that they have one life,
And also, I kind of like this life once,
I like people, people, people,
I think it's a life in which we cherish and value all kinds of people,
That's part of it.
I think it's good that it changes depending on how you sing it,
I think it's good that it changes depending on the way you sing.
So everyone loves that life.
That's right.
That's really nice.
I knew it.
And this saying, "Laughing flowers and greens will be blown away," is a proverb I really like,
Yeah.
I really like the happy feeling of this song,
It's really happy, and it's really big, really big. Big,
It's a big phrase, or it's a big thing, but it reaches you,
It's very close to you, isn't it?
Yes, it is. I think it's really good that it's so big, so big, so big, but it reaches people.
It can be conveyed to anyone.
Yes, it is.
I think so.
I really envy you for being able to put it into words like that.
No, but when you chose these lyrics,
Really.
I think it's really great.
Well, thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
That's all for this time.
Okay, I'll see you next time.
Enjoy the next installment.
Hallo! Ste.
Lovable human life All schools are not high
You love me
Spiky, peculiar times.
Righteousness is in vogue
Righteousness is a fad.
Correct. It's hard to do.
It's hard to do. I'm a first-time minister.
I'm a first-time minister.
I want to take care of it.
There's a lot of colors.
I've got a good stance.
I'm ready
I want to keep it straight
The future, the future, the future, the future, the future, the future, the future, the future, the future.
I want to be a bear Life is so dark
As many yeses as I can hear
Ange Lovable
Bikibiki Bikibiki Bear life St. high
Carty, because I forgot only the warmth
And sometimes Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange, Ange.
Ange. Ange. Ange. Ange.
Bikibiki Bear Life, for example, at a theme park.
But I don't know you.
What do you bring to the park?
Are you the kind of person who can turn around?
What you say is up to you
This and that.
You know who?
Sleep at the bottom
At this intersection
When you turn
Who do you think you'll run into?
I know money money
You are right
At the end of the day
Good luck good luck
I hope so
Oh!
I'm true!
I'm a money money human life
I'm a money money money human life
Simple, simple, simple, simple, simple
Merry Garlic
And that's why I love life
Boom, boom, boom, starch
It's a hot adventure. Stop what you're doing.
Open the front door and love the universe
Human life to love
Osaki was a mankey
I'm trying to be
YES! You're beautiful if you don't brag
I'm so beautiful, beautiful, beautiful You are life
The road ahead is not so high
I'll never forget your warmth
I'm you, I'm you, I'm you, I'm you
I'm you I'm you I'm you I'm you I'm you
Lady!
Good luck tomorrow!
This program is brought to you by Sakura Ishiyama of Juice Juice and Sumire Tashiro of Ocha no Oma.
and Sumire Tashiro from Ochanomama.
It's time for the ending!
Here is an announcement!
Juice Juice's best selection album
Juice Story is now on sale!
It's an album that contains 10 years of Juice Juice's history.
It also includes newly arranged versions of some of the songs.
Please listen to it!
And next week on December 6
Juice Juice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour
Juice Juice at Budokan will be released on DVD and Blu-ray!
It was a very fun concert!
We hope you can watch it many times on DVD!
Ochanoumi's first album Channel 1 will be released on January 10 next year!
This will be our first album, so please listen to it!
Wednesday, December 6 at Nippo Budokan
JuiceJuice 10th Anniversary Concert Tour 2023 Final
Juice Story will be held!
As you can see on the album, this concert will be filled with a lot of history of JuiceJuice.
We will do our best to let many people know more about our history!
Please come and see us!
On December 21, JuiceJuice Ochanoma will perform at Cho-Idol Fest!
We will be performing at the Omiya Sonic City Grand Hall.
It will be a very fun festival, so we hope you will come and join us!
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 ofus will start on January 2nd next year!
We will be performing with 3 groups!
Haloste is a channel where Hello Project members will be appearing more and more!
New videos will be uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel!
This time we have Sakura Ishiyama from JuiceJuice and Sumire Tashiro from Ochamama.
and Sumire Tashiro from Ochanomama.
Good bye.
Thank you for watching!